{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian6.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Sono di Firenze",
                "Io sono di Firenze",
                "Sono di Florenze"
            ],
            "answer": "Io sono di Firenze.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517337313.0766878,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I'm from Florence.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Di chi sono i piatti?",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1517337721.8065233,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Whose dishes are they?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i piatti sono di Nicola",
                "I piatti sono di Nicola"
            ],
            "answer": "I piatti sono di Nocola.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1517337579.6352336,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The dishes are Nicola's.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la scrivania di Anna e' in camera sua",
                "La scrivania di Anna e' in camera sua"
            ],
            "answer": "La scrivania di Anna e' in camera sua.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1517337707.2671793,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Anna's desk is in her room.\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In soggiorno ci sono le sedie",
                "in soggiorno ci sono le sedie"
            ],
            "answer": "In soggiorno ci sono le sedie.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517337588.47513,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the living room there are the chairs.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "questa e' la casa di Paolo e Marta",
                "Questa e' la casa di Paolo e Marta"
            ],
            "answer": "Questa e' la casa di Paolo e Marta.",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1517337678.5027623,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"This is Paolo and Marta's house.\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i libri di Marta sono in soggiorno"
            ],
            "answer": "I libri di Marta sono in soggiorno.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1517337528.6913786,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Marta's books are in the living room.\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In bagno c'e la doccia",
                "in bagno c'e la doccia"
            ],
            "answer": "In bagno c'e' la doccia.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517337601.875261,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the bathrrom there is the shower.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il tappeto",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1517337938.2892401,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the rug\"?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In bagno ci sono gli asciugamani",
                "in bagno ci sono gli asciugamani"
            ],
            "answer": "In bagno ci sono gli asciugamani.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517337894.4654622,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the bathroom there are the towels.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i cuscini",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1517337837.817636,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the pillows\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "E' di Ann"
            ],
            "answer": "E' di Ann.",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1517337930.1094928,
            "question": "Given the definition \"It is Ann's.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il tavolo"
            ],
            "answer": "il travolo",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517337742.3943815,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the table\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Anna e' in bagno"
            ],
            "answer": "Anna e' in bagno.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517337875.2216966,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Anna is in the bathroom.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here is the house of Paolo and Marta",
                "This is Paolo and Marta's house",
                "Here is Paolo and Marta's house"
            ],
            "answer": "This is Paolo and Marta's house.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517337923.0215728,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Questa e' la casa di Paolo e Marta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "armadio",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517337866.8295074,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"wardrobe\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le sedie",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338037.336915,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the chairs\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Anna's desk is in her room"
            ],
            "answer": "Anna's desk is in her room.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338035.02522,
            "question": "Given the definition \"La scrivania di Anna e' in camera sua.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sono di Nicola"
            ],
            "answer": "Sono di Nicola.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338056.4602795,
            "question": "Given the definition \"They are Nicola's.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in giardino ci sono i fiori",
                "In giardino ci sono i fiori"
            ],
            "answer": "In giardino ci sono i fiori.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517338152.0565128,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the garden there are the flowers.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "essere",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338110.4840448,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to be\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro sono in soggiorno"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro sono in soggiorno.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338047.3206089,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They are in the living room.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono di",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338108.0529344,
            "question": "The cups are Michael's. Le tazze ___ Michael.",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu sei di filadelfia",
                "Tu sei di Filadelfia"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu sei di Filadelfia.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517338157.4200804,
            "question": "Given the definition \"You're from Philadelphia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pans",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338437.534719,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pentole\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'armadio",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338435.3589747,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the closet\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in camera da letto c'e il letto di matrimoniale"
            ],
            "answer": "In camera da letto c'e' il letto matrimoniale.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338403.2631185,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the bedrrom there is the double bed.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il divano",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338432.5666685,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the couch\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Paolo e Marta sono in casa",
                "Paolo e Marte sono in casa"
            ],
            "answer": "Paolo e Marta sono in casa.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338180.8881555,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Paolo and Marta are at home.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Marta e' in giardino"
            ],
            "answer": "Marta e' in giardino.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338198.7518723,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Marta is in the garden.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Di chi e' la lavatrice"
            ],
            "answer": "Di chi e' la lavatrice?",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517338443.3588078,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Whose washing machine is it?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cucina",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338388.8152225,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"kitchen\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in cucina c'e il tavolo"
            ],
            "answer": "In cucina c'e' il travolo.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338530.5944972,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the kitchen there is the table.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am at home"
            ],
            "answer": "I am at home.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338590.669615,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io sono a casa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338506.7181003,
            "question": "I am in the kitchen. Io ___ in cucina.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In camera da letto c'e"
            ],
            "answer": "In camera (da letto) c'e'...",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338581.0543482,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the bedroom there is...\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io sono a casa",
                "sono in casa"
            ],
            "answer": "Io sono a casa.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338539.7742622,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am at home.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la stanza",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517338583.677766,
            "question": "Given the definition \"room\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in soggiorno c'e"
            ],
            "answer": "In soggiorno c'e'...",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338451.2986813,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the living room there is...\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Lei e'",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338587.1339116,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you are (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "rug"
            ],
            "answer": "the rug",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338766.5731509,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il tappeto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la lavatrice e' di Ann",
                "La lavatrice e' di Ann"
            ],
            "answer": "La lavatrice e' di Ann.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338880.3162086,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The washing machine is Ann's.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le pentole",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338772.4130678,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the pans\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Paolo e Marta hanno una figlia: Anna"
            ],
            "answer": "Paolo e Marta hanno una figlia: Anna.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338831.4328043,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Paolo and Marta have a daughter: Anna.\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "voi siete",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338887.893263,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you are (plural)\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In camera ci sono i cuscini"
            ],
            "answer": "In camera ci sono i cuscini.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517338898.4286687,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the bedroom there are the pillows.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il tappeto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338776.7809355,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the carpet\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the pans",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338820.8849218,
            "question": "Given the definition \"le pentole\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The washing machine is Ann's",
                "The washing machine is Anns"
            ],
            "answer": "The washing machine is Ann's.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517338996.0717366,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La lavatrice e' di Ann.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chairs",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338956.5639637,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sedie\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Marta's books are in the living room"
            ],
            "answer": "Marta's books are in the living room.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338938.552318,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I libri di Marta sono in soggiorno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Nicola's plates"
            ],
            "answer": "Nicola's dishes",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338905.748395,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i piatti di Nocola\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Le tazze di Paolo sono in cucina"
            ],
            "answer": "Le tazze di Paolo sono in cucina.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338954.0443993,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Paolo's cups are in the kitchen.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "closet"
            ],
            "answer": "wardrobe",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338963.5481405,
            "question": "Given the definition \"armadio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Paolo e' in camera"
            ],
            "answer": "Paolo e' in camera da letto.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338975.8355453,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Paolo is in the bedroom.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "she is",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517338940.6806567,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lei e'\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the room"
            ],
            "answer": "room",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339093.6475387,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la stanza\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In the kitchen is the table"
            ],
            "answer": "In the kitchen there is the table.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517339119.4552312,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In cucina c'e' il travolo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gli asciugamani",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517339131.9071982,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the towels\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "They are Nicola's"
            ],
            "answer": "They are Nicola's.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517339140.0193028,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sono di Nicola.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "loro sono",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517339143.146903,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"they are\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in the bathroom is the shower",
                "In the bathroom there is the shower"
            ],
            "answer": "In the bathrrom there is the shower.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517339128.1470983,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In bagno c'e' la doccia.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lo specchio"
            ],
            "answer": "lo speechio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517339134.9872768,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the mirror\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le pentole"
            ],
            "answer": "pentole",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339010.0681112,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"pans\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le,i,il"
            ],
            "answer": "le, i, il",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339227.2390041,
            "question": "In the kitchen there are the cups, the dishes, and the table. In cucina ci sono ___ tazze, ___ piatti e ___ travolo.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gli asciugamani"
            ],
            "answer": "asciugamani",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339237.2067945,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"towels\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the rug"
            ],
            "answer": "the carpet",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339438.3173518,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il tappeto\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tu sei",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339146.0192416,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"you are (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In the living room there are the chairs"
            ],
            "answer": "In the living room there are the chairs.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339458.0010915,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In soggiorno ci sono le sedie.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lei e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339161.1033397,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"she is\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In the room there are the pillows",
                "In the bedroom there are the pillows"
            ],
            "answer": "In the bedroom there are the pillows.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517339471.1292467,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In camera ci sono i cuscini.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i piatti",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339158.103206,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the dishes\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Ann's washing machine",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339493.0298877,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la lavatrice di Ann\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "couch"
            ],
            "answer": "the couch",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339509.0653062,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il divano\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "plates",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339504.133312,
            "question": "Given the definition \"piatti\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I am",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339511.5775247,
            "question": "Given the definition \"io sono\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "camera",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339474.7211666,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"bedroom\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "soggiorno"
            ],
            "answer": "il soggiorno",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339498.2612283,
            "question": "Given the definition \"living room\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in cucina ci sono"
            ],
            "answer": "In cucina ci sono ...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339481.5891976,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the kitchen there are...\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la lavatrice",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339501.8531148,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the washing machine\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i piatti di Nicola"
            ],
            "answer": "i piatti di Nocola",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339517.625253,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Nicola's dishes\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In the bathroom there are the towels"
            ],
            "answer": "In the bathroom there are the towels.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339613.5604582,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In bagno ci sono gli asciugamani.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bed",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339520.7761078,
            "question": "Given the definition \"letto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "kitchen",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339593.8039947,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cucina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lui e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339590.628499,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"he is\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "he is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339587.188967,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lui e'\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Marta is in the garden"
            ],
            "answer": "Marta is in the garden.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339585.4728937,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Marta e' in giardino.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In the bedroom there is the double bed"
            ],
            "answer": "In the bedrrom there is the double bed.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339603.5248425,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In camera da letto c'e' il letto matrimoniale.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "La lavatrice di Ann"
            ],
            "answer": "la lavatrice di Ann",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339662.4687972,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ann's washing machine\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bedroom",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339643.5325718,
            "question": "Given the definition \"camera\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in the garden there are the flowers"
            ],
            "answer": "In the garden there are the flowers.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339653.268418,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In giardino ci sono i fiori.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "we are in the bedroom"
            ],
            "answer": "We are in the bedroom.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339668.904494,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi siamo in camera da letto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the armoir"
            ],
            "answer": "the closet",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339627.8414762,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'armadio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "plates"
            ],
            "answer": "the dishes",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339656.5963311,
            "question": "Given the definition \"i piatti\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "io sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339619.0484052,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui e' in cucina"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui e' in bagno.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339672.4484093,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He is in the kitchen.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the living room"
            ],
            "answer": "living room",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339727.360221,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il soggiorno\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "letto"
            ],
            "answer": "il letto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339730.8159873,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the bed\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sedie",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339721.3842227,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"chairs\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the kitchen"
            ],
            "answer": "kitchen",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339681.9369147,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la cucina\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the bed",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339685.0403779,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il letto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339717.252259,
            "question": "She is in the bathroom. Lei ___ in bagno.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in the bedroom",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339676.8716362,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"in camera (da letto)\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Paolo and Marta have a daughter: Anna"
            ],
            "answer": "Paolo and Marta have a daughter: Anna.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339711.1730413,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Paolo e Marta hanno una figlia: Anna.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am from Florence"
            ],
            "answer": "I'm from Florence.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339738.440082,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Io sono di Firenze.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "camera, sono, "
            ],
            "answer": "camera, sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339764.4195182,
            "question": "In the bedrrom there are the pillows, the closet, and the bed. In ___ da letto ci ___ i cuscini, l'armadio e il letto.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the chairs",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339733.2404907,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le sedie\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in the living room",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339771.007909,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"in soggiorno\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i, di"
            ],
            "answer": "I, di",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339747.363519,
            "question": "The pillows are Paolo's. ___ cuscini sono ___ Paolo.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "You are from Philadelphia"
            ],
            "answer": "You're from Philadelphia.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339783.2075276,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Tu sei di Filadelfia.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "we are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339741.015812,
            "question": "Given the definition \"noi siamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the washing machine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339775.9759529,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la lavatrice\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bedroom",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339806.0996687,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la camera da letto or camera\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in the bathroom there is"
            ],
            "answer": "In the bathroom there is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339816.3319848,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In bagno c'e'...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "towels",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339787.0475416,
            "question": "Given the definition \"asciugamani\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "towels"
            ],
            "answer": "the towels",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339809.9798086,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gli asciugamani\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i piatti"
            ],
            "answer": "piatti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339802.0835965,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"plates\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in camera da letto"
            ],
            "answer": "in camera (da letto)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339791.7761464,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in the bedroom\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the bathroom"
            ],
            "answer": "bathrrom",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339820.531794,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il bagno\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "camera"
            ],
            "answer": "la camera da letto or camera",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339798.1968875,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bedroom\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in the living room there is"
            ],
            "answer": "In the living room there is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339841.168087,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In soggiorno c'e'...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the table",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339844.543655,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il travolo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cucina"
            ],
            "answer": "la cucina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339856.3474338,
            "question": "Given the definition \"kitchen\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Who's washing machine is this?"
            ],
            "answer": "Whose washing machine is it?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339832.9357316,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Di chi e' la lavatrice?\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Paolo is in the bedroom"
            ],
            "answer": "Paolo is in the bedroom.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339853.2433786,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Paolo e' in camera da letto.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "they are in the living room"
            ],
            "answer": "They are in the living room.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339862.083591,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro sono in soggiorno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in bagno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339835.519538,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in the bathroom\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Paolo's cups are in the kitchen"
            ],
            "answer": "Paolo's cups are in the kitchen.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339875.9395328,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Le tazze di Paolo sono in cucina.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "letto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339878.1953561,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"bed\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "you are (formal)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339924.1073723,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei e'\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the mirror",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517339928.0191476,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lo speechio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339900.263207,
            "question": "Given the definition \"essere\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in the kitchen there are"
            ],
            "answer": "In the kitchen there are...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339884.3673162,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In cucina ci sono ...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "he is in the bathroom"
            ],
            "answer": "He is in the kitchen.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339891.736061,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui e' in bagno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "they are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339920.7313595,
            "question": "Given the definition \"loro sono\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "bagno"
            ],
            "answer": "il bagno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339918.3390236,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bathrrom\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "noi siamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339930.8672469,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"we are\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "It is Ann's"
            ],
            "answer": "It is Ann's.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339982.3467786,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"E' di Ann.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in bagno c'e"
            ],
            "answer": "In bagno c'e'...",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517340010.7988532,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the bathroom there is...\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Paolo and Marta are at home"
            ],
            "answer": "Paolo and Marta are at home.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517340005.7745261,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Paolo e Marta sono in casa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "siamo in camera da letto",
                "noi siamo in camera da letto"
            ],
            "answer": "Noi siamo in camera da letto.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517340019.4748993,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We are in the bedroom.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "y'all are"
            ],
            "answer": "you are (plural)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339958.063087,
            "question": "Given the definition \"voi siete\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the plates are Nicola's"
            ],
            "answer": "The dishes are Nicola's.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339937.6787474,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I piatti sono di Nocola.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in the bathroom",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517339963.3992538,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"in bagno\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pillows"
            ],
            "answer": "the pillows",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517340054.1670382,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i cuscini\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Who's plates are these?"
            ],
            "answer": "Whose dishes are they?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517340028.6266956,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Di chi sono i piatti?\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "In the bedroom there is"
            ],
            "answer": "In the bedroom there is...",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517340040.8622727,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In camera (da letto) c'e'...\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you are"
            ],
            "answer": "you are (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517340044.3663487,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tu sei\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sei",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517340048.2142122,
            "question": "You are in the living room. Tu ___ in soggiorno.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in soggiorno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517340056.7829516,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in the living room\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Anna is in the bathroom"
            ],
            "answer": "Anna is in the bathroom.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517340034.9620092,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Anna e' in bagno.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        }
    ]
}